<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Software Development Projects on Wonyoung Jang</title>
    <link>https://wonyoungjang.org/categories/software-development-projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Software Development Projects on Wonyoung Jang</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://wonyoungjang.org/categories/software-development-projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Realtime Multiplayer Drawing App</title>
      <link>https://wonyoungjang.org/pages/realtime-multiplayer-drawing-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wonyoungjang.org/pages/realtime-multiplayer-drawing-app/</guid>
      <description>Draw in realtime on a blank canvas with others on the same server.
Introduction This project is a fork of GitHub - mayfer/claude-app-generator-demo, which was a demonstration of Anthropic&amp;rsquo;s Claude 3 Opus generating an app in one go without errors. You can see a demonstration of the generation and the program here: murat on Twitter.
Why Did I Fork This? While the demonstration shows no errors, the instructions in the README were incomplete, and others had trouble with installing the dependencies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Website</title>
      <link>https://wonyoungjang.org/pages/this-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wonyoungjang.org/pages/this-website/</guid>
      <description>This page is a meta presentation for the deployment of this website (and this page).
How It&amp;rsquo;s Made Pages (notes, articles, projects) are written in Logseq markdown.
Pages with a public property are exported and converted to Hugo markdown using the Logseq Schrödinger plugin.
The exported assets and pages folders are placed in the content folder of this Hugo site.
hugo -D + hugo serve -D to build and serve the site locally.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FIRST LEGO League Challenge Q-Learning Event Scheduler</title>
      <link>https://wonyoungjang.org/pages/first-lego-league-challenge-q-learning-event-scheduler/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wonyoungjang.org/pages/first-lego-league-challenge-q-learning-event-scheduler/</guid>
      <description>A FLLC event scheduler using Q-Learning.
Update 2024-03-18: Minimally reformatted and refactored. Organization I couldn&amp;rsquo;t do in the one month span to complete a functional product for the course. Began writing out a brief history on this project.A Brief History A Nerd Snipe from a Coworker My coworker nerd sniped me with this problem: Given a set of constraints, can you devise a way to create schedule for the FIRST LEGO League Challenge event we&amp;rsquo;re running later this year?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Save Top Level Reddit Comments</title>
      <link>https://wonyoungjang.org/pages/save-top-level-reddit-comments/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wonyoungjang.org/pages/save-top-level-reddit-comments/</guid>
      <description>Extract the parent comments of a reddit post.
Premise Sometimes I just want the top voted parent comments of a reddit post.
Conclusion This tool, which let&amp;rsquo;s me save as many as I want to a CSV file, so that I can work with the data outside of reddit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Logseq Markdown Tokenizer</title>
      <link>https://wonyoungjang.org/pages/logseq-markdown-tokenizer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wonyoungjang.org/pages/logseq-markdown-tokenizer/</guid>
      <description>Estimate the cost of tokenizing markdown files for OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s text-embedding models.
The Problem Logseq does not have a native way to view the character count of your notes (aka pages).
Logseq&amp;rsquo;s performance is a balance between the number of pages and the size of each page.
Logseq&amp;rsquo;s graph is difficult to search and prune manually.
Proposed Solution Encode Logseq&amp;rsquo;s graph to enable semantic search, then leverage this encoding to develop an automatic pruning tool of some kind.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
